so the course of the last few years
while I've been working on projects and
come up with ways to make money there's
a few ideas that I've had that involve
delivery so creating food in your own
kitchen if I want to make juice and make
enough for my neighbors and delivering
it to them it always seems like delivery
is very much an added on perk that
people want but also it just is so
costly to have that in your business and
one of the things that I was AI came up
with was this idea of a hub so I
remember because it was so long ago that
I came up with it exactly how it goes
but let me just try having so everyone
who makes stuff in their own kitchen in
their own places has a specific delivery
our story pickup day those things are
then organized and you then get a
delivery on a different day so people
both a producer and consumer without
having better words for those things so
you make yogurt your neighbor makes
scarves whatever happens being your
ordering from each other and pane with
an online system we're a small fraction
would go to keeping the site but you're
actually getting it delivered to your
home and you know that your delivery
date is every Wednesday so you fill the
box with it and you pay certain amount
for delivery let's say $10 for the box
so you know you can fill that up so it
just is way more efficient it's a more
efficient and going to the grocery store
because one driver as the entire
neighborhood I don't think it's
something that would start there's a
reason Amazon waited to create delivery
until they were much bigger because you
need to have a much bigger system in
order to justify that but a delivery hub
system where everything gets the price I
called the hubs everything gets picked
up and taken to a central location
organized and brought out so there's
like a - if you're both consumer and
producer your stuff would be everyone's
like everyone's stuffs picked up on
Wednesday and delivered on Thursday so
hub delivery is Apple number 38